A Guide to the Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club Records, 1971-2018
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club Records, 1971-2018
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 05-68
1.5 linear feet
The Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club Records consists of 1.5 linear feet and spans the years 1971-2018 and contains minutes, yearbooks, photographs, scrapbooks, correspondence, directories, name tags, and a rubber stamp.
Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club on July 19, 2018.
Historical and Biographical Information
The Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club of Annandale, Virginia was organized in 1971 to stimulate interest in gardening, promote horticultural best practices, share a love of creating handicrafts, and to improve and beautify the landscape in the Sleepy Hollow Woods neighborhood. Members hosted meetings in their homes, held luncheons and parties, toured historic sites, and maintained an active presence supporting the neighborhood. The club disbanded in Summer 2018 and the group assembled one final time to donate their records to the Virginia Room on July 19, 2018.
Scope and Content
The Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club Records consists of 1.5 linear feet and spans the years 1971-2018 and contains minutes, yearbooks, photographs, scrapbooks, correspondence, directories, name tags, and a rubber stamp. Scrapbooks contain photographs of past-presidents, members, activities, parties, tours, yard sales, luncheons, and meetings. Also included is a CD-ROM containing digitized images taken by Dottye Stacy of the construction of Murray Lane and her house from 1959-1967, and a DVD entitled “The Four Seasons of Sleepy Hollow Woods.” Subjects include the history of the Sleepy Hollow Woods neighborhood in Annandale, Virginia.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Annandale (Va.) - History; Gardening - Societies, etc. - Virginia; Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club
Container List
- Member name tags, Undated (Box 1)
- Minutes binder, 1971-1984 (Box 1)
- Minutes binder, 1984-1991 (Box 1)
- Minutes binder, 1997-2005 (Box 1)
- Minutes binder, 1974, 2001-2011 (Box 2)
- Minutes binder, 2011-2018 (Box 2)
- Scrapbook Volume 1, 1990 May-1994 September (Box 3)
- Scrapbook Volume 2, 1994 October-2004 December (Box 3)
- Yearbooks, 1993-1994, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous photographs, 1994-2003 (Box 3)
- Rubber stamp, "The Sleepy Hollow Woods Garden and Craft Club Annandale, Va.", Undated (Box 3)